{
    "subject": "resource/Questacon",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/homepage",
    "object": "http://www.questacon.edu.au/",
    "human_readable": "The homepage of Questacon is http://www.questacon.edu.au/.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.955793559551239,
            "question": "What type of institution is likely represented by the URL http://www.questacon.edu.au/?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9434197545051575,
            "question": "What is the URL of the Questacon homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9093310236930847,
            "question": "Is Questacon a website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.88836669921875,
            "question": "What is the purpose of a website like Questacon.edu.au?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8665831685066223,
            "question": "What kind of information might you find on the Questacon website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8322842717170715,
            "question": "Where can you find information about Questacon online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8320634961128235,
            "question": "Is Questacon located in Australia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7910234928131104,
            "question": "Based on the URL, what can you infer about Questacon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10948725789785385,
            "question": "Does this URL belong to an educational organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07963326573371887,
            "question": "Could this URL lead to information about science exhibitions?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The homepage of Questacon is http://www.questacon.edu.au/.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2380_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does this URL belong to an educational organization?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2380_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Based on the URL, what can you infer about Questacon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2380_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Questacon located in Australia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2380_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2380_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2380_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2380_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2380_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2380_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2380_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2380_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2380_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2380_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2380_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n\n\nNone of the provided documents contain the URL for Questacon's homepage. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's my response to your query:\n\nQuery: The homepage of Questacon is http://www.questacon.edu.au.\n\nResponse:\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nReasoning: None of the documents mention the URL of the homepage of Questacon."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents mention the homepage of Questacon or provide any information that would support the statement that it is \"http://www.questacon.edu.au/\". Therefore, based on the given context, the answer is \"no.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}